http://www.myrecycledbags.com/privacy-policy

My Recycled Bags.com
Come Learn and Share Information about Recycling, Crocheting & Recycled Crafting
Home
My Contact
My Products
My Patterns
Come Learn and Share Information about Recycling, Crocheting & Green Crafting
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy for MyRecycledBags.com
The privacy of our visitors to MyRecycledBags.com is important to us.
At MyRecycledBags.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit MyRecycledBags.com, and how we safeguard your information.
We never sell your personal information to third parties.
Log Files
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.
The information in the log files include
your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.
Cookies and Web Beacons
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.
This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.
We also use third party advertisements on MyRecycledBags.com to support our site.
Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.
This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).
DoubleClick DART cookies
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements).
This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (interest based targeting).
The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey).
DART uses non personally identifiable information.
It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.
You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx
You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.
However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.
This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program.
Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. You may also request to export your personal data and/or have it deleted from this site.
MyRecycledBags.com reserves the right to change or update this privacy policy without further notice.
Pages
About Me
How to Make Plarn Yarn
My Contact
My Patterns
My Products
Terms of Use
Categories
[—]2020
(21)
December
(1)
November
(2)
October
(2)
September
(2)
August
(2)
July
(2)
June
(1)
May
(1)
April
(2)
March
(2)
February
(2)
January
(2)
[+]2019
(25)
December
(2)
November
(2)
October
(2)
September
(2)
August
(1)
July
(3)
June
(2)
May
(3)
April
(2)
March
(2)
February
(2)
January
(2)
[+]2018
(30)
December
(3)
November
(3)
October
(2)
September
(3)
August
(2)
July
(2)
June
(2)
May
(3)
April
(2)
March
(3)
February
(3)
January
(2)
[+]2017
(34)
December
(3)
November
(3)
October
(3)
September
(2)
August
(3)
July
(2)
June
(3)
May
(3)
April
(3)
March
(3)
February
(3)
January
(3)
[+]2016
(39)
December
(4)
November
(3)
October
(3)
September
(3)
August
(3)
July
(4)
June
(3)
May
(3)
April
(4)
March
(3)
February
(2)
January
(4)
[+]2015
(37)
December
(4)
November
(3)
October
(3)
September
(3)
August
(3)
July
(3)
June
(3)
May
(3)
April
(4)
March
(2)
February
(3)
January
(3)
[+]2014
(33)
December
(2)
November
(3)
October
(3)
September
(3)
August
(3)
July
(3)
June
(3)
May
(2)
April
(2)
March
(3)
February
(3)
January
(3)
[+]2013
(42)
December
(3)
November
(3)
October
(4)
September
(3)
August
(3)
July
(3)
June
(4)
May
(4)
April
(4)
March
(5)
February
(3)
January
(3)
[+]2012
(44)
December
(3)
November
(4)
October
(4)
September
(4)
August
(3)
July
(3)
June
(3)
May
(4)
April
(4)
March
(4)
February
(4)
January
(4)
[+]2011
(50)
December
(3)
November
(4)
October
(5)
September
(3)
August
(5)
July
(5)
June
(4)
May
(4)
April
(4)
March
(3)
February
(4)
January
(6)
[+]2010
(69)
December
(4)
November
(4)
October
(4)
September
(6)
August
(5)
July
(6)
June
(7)
May
(6)
April
(7)
March
(7)
February
(7)
January
(6)
[+]2009
(58)
December
(6)
November
(5)
October
(6)
September
(4)
August
(5)
July
(5)
June
(4)
May
(6)
April
(5)
March
(5)
February
(3)
January
(4)
[+]2008
(64)
December
(5)
November
(8)
October
(4)
September
(5)
August
(5)
July
(6)
June
(6)
May
(6)
April
(6)
March
(5)
February
(4)
January
(4)
[+]2007
(63)
December
(6)
November
(5)
October
(6)
September
(8)
August
(4)
July
(4)
June
(4)
May
(4)
April
(7)
March
(8)
February
(5)
January
(2)
Meta
Log in
Entries RSS
Comments RSS
WordPress.org
About Me Hello, I’m Cindy or aka RecycleCindy. Welcome to my blog site that is dedicated to recycling and crafting. I love to crochet and create crafts and other useful things from recycled materials. I share many free tutorials and patterns for creating recycled projects as well as other handmade items.
Here is a direct link to all my free patterns available here on My Recycled Bags.
Thank you for stopping by to visit and for your interest in My Recycled Bags!
Popular Posts
Double Layered Waffle Towel Topper Pattern
Crocheted Ribbed Hat Pattern
Men’s Crocheted Fingerless Gloves
Double Layer Towel Toppers
Recent CommentsCindy on VCR Tape Designer BagCindy on Crocheted Ribbed Hat PatternCindy on Double Layered Waffle Towel Topper PatternVicky Reinert on VCR Tape Designer BagCris on Double Layered Waffle Towel Topper Pattern
© 2009 My Recycled Bags.com - Powered by Wordpress.
Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
